Joaquin Sateler Villanueva

DEGREE IN PSYCHOLOGY & B.A. SOCIAL SCIENCES

ABOUT

Degree in Psychology with training in social sciences. I have interests in various technologies, such as AI, and how to put them to service for people, guided by what fields like Human-Computer Interaction and User Experience (UX) teach us, among others.

Portfolio: cacosat.com

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth: February 11, 1998

RUT: 19.890.208-K Phone: +56 9 621 428 35 Email: jsateler1@uc.cl

SKILLS

Advance Figma

Intermediate Excel

Intermediate JavaScript

Intermediate HTML & CSS

Intermediate React

Advanced English













EDUCATION

2020 - 2022

Health Psychology

Pontificia Universidad Católica de Chile

2017 - 2020

Bachelor In Social Sciences

Pontificia Universidad Católica de Chile

WORK EXPERIENCE

December 2022 - October 2024

Medible - UX Research

I performed various roles, primarily a researcher and designer, participating in the whole product development cycle, from initial research and design to design handoffs, and some project management, along with using different tools and technologies.

August 2024

The Strainer - Frontend Intern

Part-time frontend intern focused on maintaining and improving the UI of a SaaS application using JavaScript, React, Material UI, and Tailwind.

May 2023 - July 2023

Reuse - HR Consultant

Human resources consultant focused on job descriptions, performance evaluation, and onboarding, among other things.

ADDITIONAL TRAINING

2023 - 2024

The Complete Web Developer In 2023

Taught by Zero to Mastery on Udemy

2023

Complete Web & Mobile Designer In 2023: **UI/UX, Figma, And More**

Taught by Zero to Mastery on Udemy

2022

User Experience Research And Design

Taught by University of Michigan on Coursera

2020

Deep Learning

Taught by DeepLearning.Al on Coursera